<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Choose Your Own Adventure!</string>
    <string name="SC00">You wake up, it’s 8:02. You have your first class at 9:30, you’re deciding what to do before then.</string>
    <string name="SC01">You go back to sleep for a bit. You wake up again, it’s 8:30.</string>
    <string name="SC02">You drift off again. You wake up with a jolt, worried you overslept, at 8:45. You feel like you really should get going.</string>
    <string name="SC03">Well you’re a beacon of sunshine, aren’t you? Fine. You go back to sleep, and wake up, prepared for the day. It’s 5:40 in the afternoon. You’ve slept through the day. Good job.</string>
    <string name="SC10">You leave your apartment at UP, and start across the campus towards the bean, hoping they have something tasty. You’re in the mood for some bacon, but ham would be nice too. You get there, and to your dismay, they have bear. Just one. It’s alive. There is a bear in the bean. It’s blocking the way between the registers and the rest of the bean.</string>
    <string name="SC11">You walk to the edge of the admittedly wide hallway, and attempt to get past the bear. It doesn’t seem to actually mind your presence, and lets you by. You breath a sigh of relief, and go to get some food. They do have bacon, sweet! They also have eggs though, and for some reason the laws of the universe allow you to take only one.</string>
    <string name="SC12">You eat the bacon. They didn’t cook it very well today. You go to leave the bean, but the bear approaches you. It seems like it can smell the meat on your breath.</string>
    <string name="SC13">You back away from the bear, and think on what to do.</string>
    <string name="SC14">You get more bacon for the bear, and approach it again. It turns to you.</string>
    <string name="SC15">You hand the bacon to the bear, and it calmly eats it from your hand. It nods at you, making a cheerful noise. You pet it briefly, and it lets you pass. You breathe a sigh of relief, and go to class.</string>
    <string name="SC16">You eat the eggs, somehow the bean managed to prepare them over hard? Or was it under easy. You decide not to dwell on it, and go to leave. Unfortunately, the bear blocks your path again. It approaches you, holding something.</string>
    <string name="SC17">The bear gets up to you, and hands you a clipboard and a pencil. It’s a poll. It asks how you liked your experience.</string>
    <string name="SC18">The bear looks at your answers, and growls. You cover yourself out of fear, but the bear just backs away and waits by the entrance again. You awkwardly pass the bear, going to your class.</string>
    <string name="SC19">The bear looks at your answers, and its eyes widen, and a smile crosses its snout. It stands on its hind legs, grabs your hand with its paw, and shakes it, before going to wait by the entrance again. You’re not sure what to do about this situation, so just pass the bear and go to your class.</string>
    <string name="SC20">You run past the bear, It turns around and makes a concerned sounding moan. You look back at it, missing the wet floor sign by the entrance. You slip backwards, and fall on your back, knocking yourself out.</string>
    <string name="SC21">You leave the bacon on the ground, and sneak past the bear. It looks over at you, confusedly, but it decides the bacon is more interesting, and goes to eat it. You breathe a sigh of relief, and go to class.</string>
    <string name="SC22">You go towards the fire exit, and find it boarded shut, with a sign reading “Due to the multiple people trying to sneak out this door, it is temporarily closed.” You look at the door, and back to the bear, your mind whirling, and you end up passing out from the stress.</string>
    <string name="SC23">You wake up. You’re a salamander napping on a rock. You move slightly to the left, to get back into the sun. All the thoughts of student loans and classes slip away as you drift back to sleep, not a worry in the world.</string>
    <string name="SC24">Thinking quick, you throw your phone at the bear. It looks over at you, annoyed, before looking back. You feel like that wasn’t a good idea.</string>
    <string name="SC25">You take off your backpack and toss it at the bear. This seems to do considerably more, as it growls, and runs towards you.</string>
    <string name="SC26">Congratulations! You’ve been mauled by a bear!</string>
    <string name="SC27">The bear reaches under its fur, and hands you a can of breath mints, before going back towards the entrance. You shrug, breathe a sigh of confused relief, and go to class.</string>
    <string name="SC28">You realize this was, in fact, a terrible idea, and run away. Nowhere else to go, you decide it’s probably smart to just go to class.</string>
    <string name="SC30">You decide getting to class early is a good idea, and head to the business building. On your way though, you see a strange box in front of the bible building. Before you go to get it though, you see a strange glint in the circular field over to the left.</string>
    <string name="SC31">You decide to look at the box. It has a lock on it, but it’s unlocked. You wonder if you should open it.</string>
    <string name="SC32">You open the box, and a dense purple gas pours out of it, making you feel rather nauseous. You stumble over, and pass out.</string>
    <string name="SC33">You decide not to mess with it, and continue on to class.</string>
    <string name="SC34">You decide you’ll turn it in later, hoping you can find the owner. You lock the box, and carry it with you to class.</string>
    <string name="SC35">Upon closer inspection, the glint in the field turns out to be an expensive looking monitor, with a cable hooked up to it. It’s turned off.</string>
    <string name="SC36">You decide to leave the monitor alone, and proceed to class.</string>
    <string name="SC37">You decide you might yoink it, and carry it with you to class.</string>
    <string name="SC38">You turn the monitor on, and a hypnotic pattern appears on it. You stare at it, fixated, until you eventually drift off to sleep</string>
    <string name="SC40">Upon arriving to the DET lab, you sit down next to your friends, and Professor Tanner stands up to address the class. He says today you won’t need your laptops today, and that you’ll be practicing self defense. You lean over and whisper to your friend that you don’t think that will help you very much. Tanner, hearing you, walks towards you and says that since there are an odd number of students, and you’ll need a partner, he’ll make an example of you first. With a wave of his hands, all the tables and chairs, except yours, slide to the corners of the room, and a red rectangle glows on the carpet. He stands at one end, and you nervously stand at the other. He summons a countdown on one of the TVs, and says whoever leaves the arena first loses.</string>
    <string name="SC41">A bell dings, and you rush towards Tanner. Unfortunately, he looks ready for you.</string>
    <string name="SC42">You attempt to punch the Professor, but upon making contact with his flawless NES-themed dress shirt, you’re launched backwards, his beautiful wardrobe too much for you. You slam against the wall, the class oooohing as you fall to the ground.</string>
    <string name="SC43">You jump up and go to kick the professor, but he simply steps to the side, as you fly past him. You crash against the computers at the end of the lab. He winces, as you might of broken something, but he’s won all the same.</string>
    <string name="SC44">A bell dings, and neither of you move. Tanner smirks, and steps forward to the middle of the arena.</string>
    <string name="SC45">Reluctantly, you step up to the middle of the arena, and meet him there. He swings one of his arms back, about to swing it forward.</string>
    <string name="SC46">You stand your ground as he approaches. Once he reaches the center of the rectangle, he breaks into a sprint towards you.</string>
    <string name="SC47">You swing your arm back, and you both launch them forwards at the same time, making contact in the middle of the arena. You lock hands, and stare dead in each-other’s eyes. You’ve engaged in a war of thumbs.</string>
    <string name="SC48">You jab your finger forward, but are quickly shut down by Tanner, who pins your thumb down effortlessly. Professor Burton materializes out of thin air and begins counting up. You struggle to break free, but he’s simply too powerful for you. Burton reaches 10, and the class roars with applause.</string>
    <string name="SC49">You lean your thumb back, as Tanner’s thumb flies towards it, unable to reach.</string>
    <string name="SC50">You manage to swing your thumb down onto his, holding it down. Professor Burton materializes out of thin air and begins counting up. It takes everything you have to hold his finger in place, and you just run out of energy as Burton reaches 10, and the class roars with applause.</string>
    <string name="SC51">You swing your thumb into his from the side, but his thumb knocks yours away so hard that you’re sent flying through the glass wall.</string>
    <string name="SC52">You hang back and think of a strategy, but before you can, his thumb flies forwards and knocks yours back, sending you flying back through the green screen as the class oooohhhs.</string>
    <string name="SC53">You attempt to shield yourself as he swings his arm forward. It never even makes contact, but the rush of wind sends you flying backwards, skidding across the carpet and over the red line.</string>
    <string name="SC54">You step slightly to the left, as Tanner flies past you, smashing through the wall, then the wall after that, and after that. You look after him, and see outside as he flies into the bible building, showing no sign of stopping. The class is silent briefly, before breaking into cheers, grabbing you and holding you in the air in victory.</string>
    <string name="SC55">Ok so you know that street fighter thing? The raging demon thing that Akuma does? He does that. It’s very cool. Also because I’m not describing tanner actually hitting you are you nuts he’d never do that that’d be so mean D: you still lost though</string>
    <string name="SCitemless">You reach around for something, but can’t find anything to defend yourself with. Tanner smirks, and claps the air in front of him, creating a sound wave, knocking you back. Find something to defend yourself with before class next time.</string>
    <string name="SCscreen">You reach around for something, and remember the screen you found. You hold it out in front of you. Tanner hesitates, not wanting to break any technology.</string>
    <string name="SC61">You stand your ground, but Tanner manages to formulate a plan. He rushes you, sweeping your legs out from below you, and grabs the monitor as you fall backwards onto the beanbag. The class claps at the grace of his moves.</string>
    <string name="SC62">You step towards Tanner, and he takes a step back, outside of the arena. He realizes what he just did, and groans. The class laughs, and both of you join in, before shaking hands and continuing with the period.</string>
    <string name="SC63">You turn the monitor on. Hypothetically. It doesn’t actually do anything. In disappointment/shame, you leave the classroom, never showing your face again.</string>
    <string name="SCbox">You reach around for something, remembering the box you found on your way to class, and pull it out.</string>
    <string name="SC64">You attempt to open the box, but realize you locked it. Tanner walks over and picks up the box, you with it, and places you both down outside the arena.</string>
    <string name="SC65">You throw the box at Tanner, who catches, and throws it back. You attempt to catch it, but it knocks you backwards, out of the arena.</string>
    <string name="SC66">You hold the box, like you’re going to use it for something. Tanner blitzes you, and grabs the box from your arms. He tears the lock off, and opens it, releasing a thick purple gas covering half the class. When it clears, Tanner is knocked out on the ground. You cheer, and the half of class that is still awake joins you.</string>
    <string name="SCmints">You reach around for something, remembering the tin of mints the bear gave you, and throw it at Tanner. You hit him square in the forehead, dazing him.</string>
    <string name="SC67">You rush to tackle him, but he steps out of the arena just as you do, causing you to fall to the floor. It’s very embarrassing all around. </string>
    <string name="SC68">You say you’re sorry, and that you probably took it too far. Tanner says it’s ok, and steps out of the arena to get headache medicine.</string>
    <string name="SCbear">You reach around for something, but can’t find anything useful to use. Tanner steps forward, and you panic about what to do, before you hear something approaching down the hallway, before crashing through the glass wall. It’s the bear! It runs towards Tanner, who panics and runs out from the class. The bear nods at you, before running after him. You stand there, in stunned confusion.</string>
</resources>